

Address: Faridabad, Haryana, India

Phone: 7289902665

Email: shivamr.kgoyal@gmail.com

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/shivamgoyall Portfolio: shivamcreator.github.io/folio

#### **SUMMARY**

Meticulous Frontend developer with 1 year of experience and passion for responsive website design and a firm believer in the mobile-first approach. I am looking for a challenging, satisfying and well-remunerative career in the field of technology that would make full use of my academic skills and demand me to refine my existing skills and pick up a few more.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# Frontend Developer

October, 2021 - Present

# OneBanc Technologies Pvt Ltd.

- Wrote clean HTML, CSS, and JS Code integrating design and product requirements with best SEO practices.
- Tested site compatibility across multiple browsers and devices, debugging issues and addressing.
- Developed a salary calculator which will show the in-hand salary of a employee if he/she associates with OneBanc. It will
  calculate taxable salary based on the salary inputs and the deductions possible like pf, standard deductions, 80C, etc. This
  will be used to calculate tax and final in-hand salary after including OneBanc cashbacks.
- Developed Aadhaar, OTP and MPIN input boxes with complete restriction to numbers alone with all the devices and browsers took into consideration and handled every edge case with best-optimized code.

# Web Development Intern

June, 2021 - August, 2021

# Diabbymate.com

- Made a replica of a website with a task to add additional features touch to slider buttons to change screen and responsiveness, implement the proposed UI/UX with shown functionalities using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.
- <a href="https://www.samsung.com/global/galaxy/galaxy-note10/">https://www.samsung.com/global/galaxy/galaxy-note10/</a>
- The replica was successfully made with all functionalities according to the UI/UX demand, and successfully added additional features as per the requirement.

# **Data Analytics Consulting Virtual Internship**

December 2020

CGPA - 8.0

#### **KPMG**

Participated in the open-access KPMG Virtual Experience Program with Inside Sherpa. Tasks Completed include:

• Data Quality Assessment, Data Insights and presentation, and Data analytics and dashboard creation.

#### SKILLS

HTML



JAVASCRIPT



WEB SCRAPPING

SQL

#### EDUCATION

B.Tech (Computer Science & Engineering)	2018 - 2022
Dronacharya College Of Engineering, Gurugram	CGPA - 8.0
XII (Senior Secondary)	2016 - 2018
D.A.V. Public School, Faridabad	72%
XII (Secondary)	2018 - 2022

# PERSONAL PROJECTS

#### Aagmi Ghatna

- Extracts annoucements from my college website and display on command line.
- Tech Stack-Python, HTML.

D.A.V. Public School, Faridabad

#### **Netflix Clone**

- Made Netflix clone in react using Rest api.
- Tech Stack- React JS, Rest api, Bootstrap.